<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Kominote Riral Teknoloji - KoRiTek</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Kominote Riral Teknoloji - KoRiTek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Lab for Rural School</title>
      <link>/project/computer-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/computer-lab/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission KORITEK (KOminoté RIral TEKnology) is non-profit organization whose primary mission is built a pathways out of computer illiterate student in rural area in Haiti by providing them with the tools needed for a better education and obviously close the technology gaps in Rural Area.
Our Work We offer computer training/classes to teachers and student in Rural Area.
Objective Build awareness of the importance of Education for Rural People as a crucial step to achieve the Millennium goals of eradicating extreme poverty and hunger and achieving universal primary education; Overcome the urban-rural education gap; Increase access to basic Education for rural people; Improve the quality of basic education in rural areas; Foster the national capacity to plan and implement basic education plans to address the learning needs of rural people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Training</title>
      <link>/project/teacher-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/teacher-training/</guid>
      <description>Teachers Training Program We understand the impact of goods teaching on student achievement, and we know, there are many challenges that the schools face in rural areas of Haiti. Most of them serve student below the poverty line, they lack resources, and the teachers are not technology literate. The first step is to train the teachers in rural areas to get them know the technology and the advantages that come with it in teaching.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>