<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kominote Riral Teknoloji - KoRiTek</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kominote Riral Teknoloji - KoRiTek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Lab for Rural School</title>
      <link>/project/computer-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/computer-lab/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission KORITEK (KOminoté RIral TEKnology) is non-profit organization whose primary mission is built a pathways out of computer illiterate student in rural area in Haiti by providing them with the tools needed for a better education and obviously close the technology gaps in Rural Area.
Our Work We offer computer training/classes to teachers and student in Rural Area.
Objective Build awareness of the importance of Education for Rural People as a crucial step to achieve the Millennium goals of eradicating extreme poverty and hunger and achieving universal primary education; Overcome the urban-rural education gap; Increase access to basic Education for rural people; Improve the quality of basic education in rural areas; Foster the national capacity to plan and implement basic education plans to address the learning needs of rural people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Delphin</title>
      <link>/directors/roger-delphin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/roger-delphin/</guid>
      <description>Roger Delphin leads KORITEK, Inc. with the belief that student in rural areas can be as productive and competitive as the student in the cities if they have the resources. Roger Delphin holds an MBA in Devry/Keller University in Database programming and Administration. He is the co-founder of Movie Lakay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenold Beauplan</title>
      <link>/directors/kenold-beauplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/kenold-beauplan/</guid>
      <description>A board member of Koritek, Kenold is the co-founder of the popular Haiti Movie Database &amp;ldquo;Movie Lakay&amp;rdquo; and the owner of Flex Web Agency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Training</title>
      <link>/project/teacher-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/teacher-training/</guid>
      <description>Teachers Training Program We understand the impact of goods teaching on student achievement, and we know, there are many challenges that the schools face in rural areas of Haiti. Most of them serve student below the poverty line, they lack resources, and the teachers are not technology literate. The first step is to train the teachers in rural areas to get them know the technology and the advantages that come with it in teaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yvens Charlot</title>
      <link>/directors/yvens-charlot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/yvens-charlot/</guid>
      <description>Yvens charlot is an active duty personal in the armed forces of the United States; He is a CompTIA Security + Certify. Yvens Charlot has a deep experience in Network Administration and satellite communication. He is working toward his bachelor degree in computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Bull Pacius</title>
      <link>/directors/pacius-john-bull/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/pacius-john-bull/</guid>
      <description>With over 15 years of experience in Information Technology, with a focus in Network Admission. The expertise of John Bull Pacius will bring KORITEK, Inc. to next level. John Bull Pierre received a bachelor degree in computer science from INUQUA university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josue Prevalus</title>
      <link>/directors/josue-prevalus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/josue-prevalus/</guid>
      <description>Josue Prevalus is the co-founder of Valeteria, a non-profit organisation focused on providing school supplies to kids in rural areas. With over 25 years of experience in the media industry across the USA, Africa and Haiti, Josue has extensive experience in Multi-Media development. He is the co-founder of Movie Lakay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesly Gelin</title>
      <link>/directors/nesly-gelin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/directors/nesly-gelin/</guid>
      <description>WeWork is creating an industry that combines hospitality, technology, construction, co-working, and software. Danny urges potential applicants to keep in mind that they needn’t be discouraged by lack of experience in a particular area, as the company is forging a path that didn’t exist previously and is always willing to teach those who possess passion for the business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:20:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/</guid>
      <description>Photos page info here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>KORITEK (KOminote RIral TEKnology) is a non-profit organization whose primary mission is to build different pathways for the technology wise illiterate students in the rural area;”Haiti”. Our main aim is to equip their schools with the tools that are really required for a better education to overcome the technology gaps in Rural Area. We provide special trainings to the respected teachers so that they may able to educate the children of Haiti in a well manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koritek Donates School Supplies</title>
      <link>/2018/03/koritek-donates-school-supplies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/koritek-donates-school-supplies/</guid>
      <description>Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koritek Visits Bocozelle, Haiti</title>
      <link>/2018/03/koritek-visits-bocozelle-haiti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/koritek-visits-bocozelle-haiti/</guid>
      <description>Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>